BOUCHRA AHARMOUCH

COMMERCIAL

Energetic and motivated sales assistant with over 2 years of experience in customer service. My communication skills are outstanding both through written and verbal means; I work hard to always ensure all necessary parties are informed and in the loop. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.



CONTACT

- +212 7 00 75 37 27
- ➤ Bouchraaharmouch2017@gmail.com
- 239 Avenue Abdelkhalak Torres

LANGUAGES

- Arabic Native Speaker
- English Fluent
- French Proficient

SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL

- Social Media Marketing
- Design Thinking
- Content Creator
- Customer Service
- Problem-Solving
- Interpersonal Communication skills
- Time Management

TECHNICAL

- Design Tools
- Microsoft office software's
- Adope photoshop/ Illustrator

INTERESRTS

- Content Creator
- Reading
- Guitarist
- E-sports

EXPERIENCE

ENGLISH - ARABIC TRANSLATOR

Upwork - Freelance

2022 - ongoing

• Translating articles, documents from English to Arabic or vice versa

CONTENT CREATOR

Upwork - Freelance

2022 - ongoing

- Social Media Assistant
- Editing videos and pictures
- · Design Logo, Poster, Business Card

SALES REPRESENTATIVE

PatBaw, Morocco PART TIME JOB

2021-2022

- Prospects strategies
- Daily Direct messages
- Content creation

SALES REPRESENTATIVE

Personal Recruitment Outsourcing (B2C) may-July 2019

- Identifying prospects (daily phone calls)
- Negotiating with customers
- Record Track

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF FUNDAMENTAL STUDIES IN ECONOMICS AND MANAGEMENT

2022- ONGOING

University Abdelmalek Essaadi Tetouan, Morocco

DIPLOMA OF GENERAL UNIVERSITY STUDIES ECONOMICS AND MANAGEMENT SCIENCES "DEUG

2019-2021

University Abdelmalek Essaadi Tetouan, Morocco

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA MANAGEMENT AND ACCOUNTING

2017-2018

Technical Highschool Moulay Youssef Tangier, Morocco